Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco Papers
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music, 1905-1968 (Box 1-106)
  - Works with opus number, 1910-1968
    - Op. 149: 2 songs by Longfellow. Nature (chorus)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal rehearsal score, see ML96.C34 no. 83
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript vocal rehearsal score (Box-folder 41/4)
    - Op. 150: Songs and processionals for a Jewish wedding (voice(s), piano or organ)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 145
    - Op. 150: Songs and processionals for a Jewish wedding. V'erastich (voice(s), piano or organ)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 41/5)
    - Op. 150: Songs and processionals for a Jewish wedding. Simeni chachosom al libecho (voice(s), piano or organ)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 41/5)
    - Op. 150: Songs and processionals for a Jewish wedding. Boruch haba b'sheim adonai (voice(s), piano or organ)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 41/5)
    - Op. 151: The book of Jonah (narrator, voices, men's chorus, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 70/3)
      - Holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 41/6)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 41/7)
    - Op. 152: Romancero gitano (chorus, guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 41/8)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 41/8)
    - Op. 153: Four Christina Rossetti songs (women's voices, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 35
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 41/9)
    - Op. 154: Three Shelly songs (women's voices, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 74
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 41/10)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 41/10)
    - Op. 155: Second piano quintet (piano, string quartet)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 70/4)
      - Parts (Box-folder 41/11)
    - Op. 156: Six pieces in form of canons (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 22
      - Printed score (Box-folder 42/1)
    - Op. 157: Six Keats settings (chorus / men's chorus)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal rehearsal score, see ML96.C34 no. 34
      - Printed piano-vocal score, All songs present except The dove (Box-folder 42/2)
    - Op. 157: Six Keats settings. Old Meg (chorus / men's chorus)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript vocal rehearsal score (Box-folder 42/2)
    - Op. 157: Six Keats settings. Happy is England (chorus / men's chorus)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript vocal rehearsal score (Box-folder 42/2)
    - Op. 158: Morning in Iowa (narrator, instrumental ensemble)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 42/3)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 70/6)
      - Holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 42/4)
      - Parts (Box-folder 42/5-7)
    - Op. 159: Toccata (on the name of Edward George Power Briggs) (organ or piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see also Op. 170: Greeting card compositions and ML96.C34 no. 165 (Box-folder 42/8)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 42/8)
    - Op. 160: Concerto sereno (guitar, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score, see ML96.C34 no. 175
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 71/1)
      - Holograph manuscript short score, see ML96.C34 no. 153
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 44/1)
      - Parts (Box 43)
      - Printed piano-guitar score (Box-folder 44/2-3)
      - Guitar part (Box-folder 44/2-3)
    - Op. 161: The Queen of Sheba (women's voices, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 38
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 45/1)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 45/1)
    - Op. 161: The Queen of Sheba. Aria (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 39
    - Op. 161: The Queen of Sheba. Aria (voice, women's chorus, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score, Unfinished (Box-folder 71/2)
    - Op. 161: The Queen of Sheba. Aria (voice, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 45/2)
    - Op. 162: Choral with variations (4 horns)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 12
      - Printed score (Box-folder 45/3)
      - Parts (Box-folder 45/3)
    - Op. 163: Songs of the Shulamite (voice, flute, harp, string quartet)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 45/4)
      - Parts (Box-folder 45/5-6)
      - Holograph manuscript score for voice, flute, and piano (Box-folder 45/7)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score for voice, flute, and piano (Box-folder 71/3)
    - Op. 164: Overture to Much ado about nothing
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 45/8)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 71/4)
      - Parts (Box-folder 45/9)
    - Op. 165: El encanto (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 45/10)
    - Op. 166: Overture to As you like it
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 71/5)
      - Parts (Box 46)
    - Op. 167: Four dances for Love's labour's lost (orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 71/6)
      - Holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 71/7)
    - Op. 168: Proverbs of Solomon (men's voices)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal rehearsal score (Box-folder 47/1)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript vocal rehearsal score (Box-folder 47/2)
    - Op. 169: Lament of David (voice, chorus)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal rehearsal score (Box-folder 47/3)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript vocal rehearsal score (Box-folder 47/4)
    - Op. 170: Greeting card compositions
      - Holograph manuscript sketches and notes; [16] p., Character pieces dedicated to various individuals, presented as greeting cards. The pieces and any sketch materials are collectively referred to as op. 170; see also Op. 159: Toccata and ML96.C34 no. 165 (Box-folder 47/5)
    - Op. 170/1: Tango (on the name of Andre Previn) (piano)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 47/6)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 47/6)
    - Op. 170/2: Serenatella (on the name of Jascha Heifetz) (violin, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 169
      - Printed score (Box-folder 47/7)
      - Violin part (Box-folder 47/7)
    - Op. 170/3: Valse (on the name of Gregor Piatigorsky) (violoncello, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 170
      - Printed score (Box-folder 47/8)
      - Violoncello part (Box-folder 47/8)
    - Op. 170/4: Mirages (on the name of Gieseking) (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 168
      - Printed score (Box-folder 47/9)
    - Op. 170/5: Tonadilla (on the name of Andrès Segovia) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 108 and Moldenhauer Archives, ML31.M6
      - Printed score (Box-folder 47/10)
    - Op. 170/6: Rondel (on the name of Siegfried Behrend) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 109
      - Printed score (Box-folder 47/11)
    - Op. 170/7: Preludio in forma di habanera (on the name on Bruno Tonnazi) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 110
      - Printed score (Box-folder 47/12)
    - Op. 170/8: Humoresque (on the name of Tossy Spivakovsky) (violin, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 47/13)
    - Op. 170/9: Fandango (on the name of Amparo Iturbi) (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 167
      - Printed score (Box-folder 47/14)
    - Op. 170/10: Lullaby (on the name of Claudia) (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 47/15)
    - Op. 170: Tanka (on the name of Isao Takahashi) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 111
      - 2 printed scores (Box-folder 47/16)
    - Op. 170/11: Etude (on the name of Jacob Gimpel) (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 47/17)
    - Op. 170/13: A canon to Robin (piano)
      - Manuscript score (Box-folder 47/18)
    - Op. 170/14: Ninna, nanna: a lullaby for Eugene (guitar)
      - Printed score, see also Moldenhauer Archives, ML31.M6 (Box-folder 47/19)
    - Op. 170/15: Song of the Azores (on the name of Enos) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 15
      - Printed score (Box-folder 47/20)
    - Op. 170/16: A fandango for Escovado (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/1)
    - Op. 170/17: Ricercare (on the name of Luigi Dallapiccola) (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 113
      - Printed score (Box-folder 48/2)
    - Op. 170/18: Choral prelude (on the name of Albert Schweitzer) (organ)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/3)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 48/3)
    - Op. 170/18: Fugue (on the name of Albert Schweitzer) (organ)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 48/4)
    - Op. 170/19: Duo-pianism: impromptu (on the names of Hans and Rosaleen Moldenhauer) (2 pianos)
      - Photocopied manuscript score, see also Moldenhauer Archives, ML31.M6 (Box-folder 48/5)
    - Op. 170/20: Little march (on the name of Scott Harrison) (piano)
      - Manuscript score, see Moldenhauer Archives, ML31.M6
    - Op. 170/21: Suite 508 (viola, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/6)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/7)
      - Viola part (Box-folder 48/6-7)
    - Op. 170/22: Slow, with variations (on the name of Nicolas Slonimsky) (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/8)
    - Op. 170/23: Intermezzo (on the name of Harvey Siegal) (violin, piano)
      - Holograph mansucript score (Box-folder 48/9)
      - Violin part (Box-folder 48/9)
    - Op. 170/24: Valse bluette (on the name of Eric Friedman) (violin, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 171
      - Violin part, see ML96.C34 no. 171
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/10)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 48/10)
      - Violin part (Box-folder 48/10)
    - Op. 170/25: Hungarian serenade (on the name of Miklos Rozsa) (violin, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/11)
      - Violin part (Box-folder 48/11)
    - Op. 170/26: La torre del diavolo (on the name of Gisella Selden-Goth) (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/12)
    - Op. 170/27: Angelus (on the name of Nino Rota-Rinaldi) (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/13)
    - Op. 170/28: Ein Quartet-Satz (on the name of Walter Arlen) (string quartet)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/14)
      - Parts (Box-folder 48/14)
    - Op. 170/29: Arabesque (on the name of Roger) (harp)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/15)
    - Op. 170/30: Melodia (on the name of Claudio Sartori) (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/16)
    - Op. 170/31: Prelude and fugue (on the name of Gerhard Albersheim) (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/17)
    - Op. 170/32: Toccata (on the name of Hugh Mullins) (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/18)
    - Op. 170/33: Canzone siciliana (on the name of Mario Gangi) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/19)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 48/19)
    - Op. 170/34: Ballatella (on the name of Christopher Parkening) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 114
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/20)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 48/20)
    - Op. 170/35: Canzonetta (on the name of Nick Rossi) (piano)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/21)
    - Op. 170/36: Sarabande (on the name of Rey de la Torre) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 115
      - Printed score (Box-folder 48/22)
    - Op. 170/37: Romanza (on the name of Oscar Ghiglia) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 116
      - Printed score (Box-folder 48/23)
    - Op. 170/38: Homage to Purcell: fantasia (on the names of Ronald and Henry) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/24)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 48/24)
    - Op. 170/39: Cancion cubana (on the name of Hector Garcia) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 117
      - Printed score (Box-folder 48/25)
    - Op. 170/40: Cancion venezuelana (on the name of Alirio Diaz) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 48/26)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 48/26)
    - Op. 170/41: Cancion argentina (on the name of Ernesto Bitteti) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 49/1)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 49/1)
    - Op. 170/42: Estudio (on the name of Manuel López Ramos) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 49/2)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 49/2)
    - Op. 170/43: Aria da Chiesa (on the name of Ruggero Chiesa) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 49/3)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 49/3)
    - Op. 170/44: Brasileira (on the name of Laurindo Almeida) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 49/4)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 49/4)
    - Op. 170/45: Second arabesque (on the name of Pearl Chertok) (harp)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 166
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 49/5)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 49/5)
    - Op. 170/46: Japanese print (on the name of Jiro Matsuda) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 49/6)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 49/6)
    - Op. 170/47: Volo d'Angeli (on the name of Angelo Gilardino) 9guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 49/7)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 49/7)
    - Op. 170/48: Canzone Calabrese (on the name of Ernest Calabria) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 49/8)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 49/8)
    - Op. 170/49: Prelude (on the name of Frederick Tulan) (organ)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 49/9)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 49/9)
    - Op. 170/50: Tarantella campana (on the name of Eugene di Novi) (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 49/10)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 49/10)
    - Op. 170/51: The Persian prince (on the name of David Blumberg) (viola, harp)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 49/11)
      - Viola part (Box-folder 49/11)
    - Op. 171: Songs of the Oceanides (voices, 2 flutes, harp)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 49/12)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 72/1)
      - Parts (Box-folder 49/12)
    - Op. 171/2: Songs of the Oceanides (voices, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 49/13)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 49/13)
      - Photocopied printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 49/13)
    - Op. 172: The song of songs (voices, chorus, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 72/2-3)
      - Parts (Box 50)
      - Parts (Box-folder 51/1-4)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal rehearsal score (Box-folder 51/5)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript vocal rehearsal score (Box-folder 72/4)
    - Op. 173: Three Shelley songs (women's voices, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 55
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 52/1)
    - Op. 174: Two motets (chorus)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal rehearsal score, see ML96.C34 no. 70
      - Printed vocal rehearsal score (Box-folder 52/2)
    - Op. 175: Six carols on early English poems (chorus)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal rehearsal score, see also ML96.C34 no. 162
      - Printed vocal rehearsal score (Box-folder 52/3)
    - Op. 176: Tre preludi mediterranei (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 24 and ML96.C34 no. 160
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 52/4)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 52/4)
    - Op. 177: Escarraman (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 36
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 52/5)
      - 2 printed scores (Box-folder 52/5)
    - Op. 178: The stories of Joseph (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 52/6)
    - Op. 179: Two sonatas. No. 1 (trumpet, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 52/7)
    - Op. 179: Two sonatas. No. 2 (trumpet, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 52/8)
      - Holograph manuscript incipits; [2] p. (Box-folder 72/5)
    - Op. 180: Passacaglia (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 155
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 52/9)
      - Manuscript score (Box-folder 52/9)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 52/9)
    - Op. 181: The merchant of Venice (voices, chorus, orchestra)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box 73)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score, Acts I and II only (Box-folder 88/1-2)
      - Holograph manuscript short score
        see ML96.C34 no. 37
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript short score (Box 74)
    - Op. 181: The merchant of Venice, Act II. Caskets scene (voices, chorus, orchestra)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 52/10)
    - Op. 181: The merchant of Venice, Act II. Nocture (voices, chorus, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 52/11)
    - Op. 181: The merchant of Venice, Act II. Epilogue (voices, chorus, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 52/12)
    - Op. 181: The merchant of Venice, Act III. Aria di Porzia (voices, chorus, orchestra)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 52/13)
    - Op.181: The merchant of Venice (voices, chorus, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript short score fragment; [1] p., At bottom: To my dear Herman... this unfinished part of the Merchant of Venice... November 24, 1956 (Box-folder 52/14)
    - Op. 182: All's well that ends well (voices, chorus, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box 75)
      - Holograph manuscript short score (Box 76)
      - Holograph manuscript piano sketch, On p. [2]: To Herman, for Backlash, November 3, 1955 (Box-folder 52/15)
    - Op. 183: The fiery furnace (narrator, children's chorus, piano or organ, percussion)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 20
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 21
      - Percussion part (Box-folder 53/1)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 77/1)
    - Op. 184: Endymion (chorus)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal rehearsal score, see ML96.C34 no. 17
    - Op. 185: Pastorale and rondo (clarinet, violin, violoncello, piano)
      - 2 holograph manuscript scores, 1 score is unfinished (Box-folder 53/2)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 77/2)
      - Parts (Box-folder 53/3)
    - Op. 186: Vogelweide (voice, guitar or piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 53/4)
      - Photocopied holograph mansucript score (Box-folder 77/3)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 53/5)
      - Photocopied printed score (Box-folder 53/5)
    - Op. 187: Sonatina zoologica (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 40
      - Printed score (Box-folder 54/1)
    - Op. 188: Il bestiario (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 54/2)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 54/3)
    - Op. 189: Poesia svedese (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 54/4)
    - Op. 189: Lauda in honore Sanctae Birgittae (women's chorus)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal rehearsal score (Box-folder 54/5)
    - Op. 190: Platero y yo (narrator, guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 172
      - Printed score, Vols. I and IV only (Box-folder 54/6)
    - Op. 190: Platero y yo. Platero (narrator, guitar)
      - Manuscript score, Includes fingerings by A. Segovia; see ML96.C34 no. 172
    - Op. 190: Platero y yo. Angelus (narrator, guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, Includes fingerings by A. Segovia; see ML96.C34 no. 172
    - Op. 190: Platero y yo. Melancolia (narrator, guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, Includes fingerings by A. Segovia; see ML96.C34 no. 172
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 54/6)
      - Manuscript score, Includes fingerings by A. Segovia; see ML96.C34 no. 172
    - Op. 190: Platero y yo. A Platero en el Cielo de Moguer (narrator, guitar)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score
    - Op. 191: Saul (voices, chorus, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box 78-79)
      - Holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 54/7-9)
    - Op. 192: Memorial service for the departed (cantor, chorus, organ)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 80
      - Photocopied printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 54/10)
    - Op. 193: Zwei Schiller Ballades. Die Kraniche des Ibykus (narrator, 2 pianos, percussion)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 54/11)
      - Percussion part (Box-folder 54/11)
    - Op. 193: Zwei Schiller Ballades. Der Handschuh (narrator, 2 pianos, percussion)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 54/12)
      - Percussion part (Box-folder 54/12)
    - Op. 194: Tre preludi al Circeo (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 23
      - Printed score (Box-folder 55/1)
    - Op. 195: 24 caprichos de Goya (guitar)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 55/2)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score, Includes notes and musical insertions (Box-folder 55/3)
      - Manuscript score, Nos. 1-3 only; see ML96.C34 no. 152
      - Printed score (Box-folder 55/4)
    - Op. 196: Sonatina canonica (2 guitars)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 151
      - Manuscript score (Box-folder 55/5)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 55/6)
    - Op. 197: Amours de Ronsard (chorus)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal score (Box-folder 55/7)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript vocal score (Box-folder 80/1)
    - Op. 198: The importance of being Ernest (voices, 2 pianos, percussion)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 80/2-4)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 55/8)
      - Percussion part (Box-folder 56/1)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 80/5-7)
    - Op. 199: Les guitares bien tempérées (2 guitars)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box 81)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 56/2)
    - Op. 200: The book of Esther (narrator, voices, chorus, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 82/1-2)
      - Holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 56/3)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 82/3)
    - Op. 201: Concerto (2 guitars, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score, see ML96.C34 no. 159
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 82/4)
      - Holograph manuscript score for 2 guitars and piano (Box-folder 56/4)
      - Printed score for 2 guitars and piano (Box-folder 56/5)
    - Op. 202: The seventh day (chorus)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal score (Box-folder 56/6)
    - Op. 203: Third string quartet
      - Holograph manuscript score, Laid in: Photocopied holograph manuscript sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 56/7)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 82/5)
      - Parts (Box-folder 56/8)
    - Op. 204: The book of Tobit (narrator, voices, chorus, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 83/1-4)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 83/5-6)